{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter10_Vocab.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "nuotare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396543.8857393,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to swim\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "andare in barca a vela",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460396555.2610834,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sail\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Le",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396549.2626681,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to you (formal)\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "basketball",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396520.1311314,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la pallacanestro, il basket\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to him",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396547.3986547,
            "question": "Given the definition \"gli\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "to share",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396523.283259,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere in comune\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to play tennis",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396534.18308,
            "question": "Given the definition \"giocare a tennis\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to understand",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396531.1066823,
            "question": "Given the definition \"capire\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to prefer",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396625.9812953,
            "question": "Given the definition \"preferire\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "finire",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396557.3822923,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to finish, to end\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "soccer",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460396673.7517374,
            "question": "Given the definition \"il calcio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "guardare lo sport in televisione",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396665.319935,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to watch sports on TV\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396668.4557395,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to you (informal)\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "gli",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460396670.7923348,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to them\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "cross-country skiing",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460396678.4235845,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sci di fondo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "giocare a tennis",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1460396689.387984,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to play tennis\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "to y'all",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396695.9155927,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to you (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396707.0875573,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "avere in comune",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396753.4742055,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to share\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "capire",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396743.3864305,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to understand\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "to sail",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396720.1355598,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"andare in barca a vela\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "il calcio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460396764.8541327,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"soccer\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "mi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396745.7058942,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to me\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "to them",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396734.6991556,
            "question": "Given the definition \"gli\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "interessi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396899.24093,
            "question": "Given the definition \"interests\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "sci di fondo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460396938.8721256,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cross-country skiing\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "to her",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396834.5857253,
            "question": "Given the definition \"le\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "a passion for",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396825.0780945,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la passione per\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "la pallacanestro, il basket",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1460396945.219768,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"basketball\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "interests",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396767.5265045,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"interessi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to swim",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396819.6528008,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nuotare\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "preferire",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460396830.9498641,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to prefer\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "to me",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396951.0032341,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "vi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396952.7722256,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to y'all\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "le",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460396980.8714232,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to her\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sci alpino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460397012.0705903,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Alpine skiing\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "la passione per",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460397022.5593548,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a passion for\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "gli",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460397003.1552508,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to him\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "to us",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460397005.2115355,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ci\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ci",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460397018.7067115,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to us\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "to finish, to end",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460397040.3026867,
            "question": "Given the definition \"finire\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Alpine skiing",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460397027.1985908,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sci alpino\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to watch sports on TV",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460397034.959067,
            "question": "Given the definition \"guardare lo sport in televisione\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to ride a bike",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1460397052.970522,
            "question": "Given the definition \"andare in bicicletta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "andare in bicicletta",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1460397100.8825872,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"to ride a bike\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "to you (informal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1460397081.2145352,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}